# **Paul Eagle**

253 Western Avenue, Port Talbot, Glamorgan SA12 7NF - 01639797255 (H) - 07786595145 (M) - paul34913@gmail.com

## **Professional Summary**

I find myself to be honest, trustworthy and a reliable person who works well both as part of a team and as an individual. I am punctual, have a good sense of timekeeping and can carry out complicated tasks with efficiency and confidence. I am available to work any overtime that is needed, am flexible in my working role, a fast learner with excellent organisational skills and can easily adjust to different working requirements. I enjoy learning new skills and am always able to achieve a high standard of work. I am competent in various computer systems and applications and have even designed and implemented my own systems in previous employment. I have a vast array of computer skills including basic programming, database creation, graphic design, web design and computer building/maintenance. I am confident that I could pick up any new system with minimal effort and time. Whilst my favoured skills are based in the office and within IT, I also have a lot of experience in heavy industries, warehouse and factory-based environments. I have driven forklift trucks of various sizes up to twelve ton and used most attachments. I am also a competent machine operator with experience in press-brake, CNC, pneumatic systems, hydraulic systems, mechanical systems, and robotic systems.

## **Experience**

Adecco @ Cultech Ltd

May 2021 to Present

## Warehouse Operator/Goods-in

Port Talbot

- Loading/Unloading of vehicles
- Checking in goods/materials
- Put away
- Stock Tracking

Smart Solutions @ Cyden Ltd

September 2020 to May 2021

#### **Material Handler**

Llansamlet, Swansea

- Picking/Dropping Down/Kitting/Returns/Despatch/Goods-in
- Loading/Unloading HGV's with Counterbalance FLT
- Put-away/Dropping-down with Reach FLT
- Use of SAGE via PDA and Desktop
- Cycle counting/Stock Check/Receipting deliveries

Ash & Lacy Ltd

February 2017 to May 2020

## **Machine Operator**

Port Talbot

- Production of sheet metal fascia's/guttering/profile sheet etc
- Repair and maintenance of machinery
- 2 Ton/7 Ton/Combi/6m Side Loader/Reach FLT Operator
- Stock management
- Vehicle Loading

**Aspire Debt Solutions** 

April 2015 to February 2017

## Administrator

Port Talbot

- Creditor and client correspondence
- Customer support and payments
- Website design/maintenance and data entry
- Customer service

#### **Core Skills**

- Administrative
- Customer Service
- Data entry
- Forklift Truck
- Health & Safety

- IT
- Machine Operator
- Manufacturing
- Production
- Warehouse

# **Education**

## **Sandfields Comprehensive**

1996

2010

Maths, Design Technology, Music, Business Studies and English

**Port Talbot** 

College

CLAIT, OCN Level 2, CLAIT +, Cambridge Certificate: Microsoft Office Suite

Neath

TATA Steel 2015

On-site Courses: 5S, Continuous Improvement, COSHH, Breathing Apparatus, Confined Space, Remote Pendant Crane, Slinging & Rigging.

**Port Talbot** 

Home Learning 2016

GCSE: Higher Physics

**Port Talbot** 

#### **Current Certifications**

**FLT Counterbalance** 

**FLT Reach** 

**MEWP** 

CSCS

HSA

First Aid

Manual Handling

## **Personal Information**

Date of Birth: 03/02/80

**Driving Licence:** Yes (Clean Licence)

Own Vehicle: Yes

## **References**

Available upon request.

#### **Interests**

Family life, computers, gadgets, guitar, music, and graphic design.